const enigmes = [

  {
    id: 1,
    question: "QUESTION 1",
    answers: ["reponse 1"],
    stops: ["ARRET A", "ARRET B", "ARRET C"],
    letter: "V",
    message: "Eh bien, ça en fait des colonnes !"
  },

  {
    id: 2,
    question: "QUESTION 2",
    answers: ["reponse 2"],
    stops: ["ARRET D", "ARRET E", "ARRET F"],
    letter: "E",
    message: "Eh bien, ça en fait des colonnes !"
  },

  {
    id: 3,
    question: "QUESTION 3",
    answers: ["reponse 3"],
    stops: ["ARRET G", "ARRET H", "ARRET I"],
    letter: "U",
    message: "Eh bien, ça en fait des colonnes !"
  },

  {
    id: 4,
    question: "QUESTION 4",
    answers: ["reponse 4"],
    stops: ["ARRET J", "ARRET K", "ARRET L"],
    letter: "X",
    message: "Eh bien, ça en fait des colonnes !"
  },

  {
    id: 5,
    question: "QUESTION 5",
    answers: ["reponse 5"],
    stops: ["ARRET M", "ARRET N", "ARRET O"],
    letter: "T",
    message: "Eh bien, ça en fait des colonnes !"
  },

  {
    id: 6,
    question: "QUESTION 6",
    answers: ["reponse 6"],
    stops: ["ARRET P", "ARRET Q", "ARRET R"],
    letter: "U",
    message: "Eh bien, ça en fait des colonnes !"
  },

  {
    id: 7,
    question: "QUESTION 7",
    answers: ["reponse 7"],
    stops: ["ARRET S", "ARRET T", "ARRET U"],
    letter: "E",
    message: "Eh bien, ça en fait des colonnes !"
  },

  {
    id: 8,
    question: "QUESTION 8",
    answers: ["reponse 8"],
    stops: ["ARRET V", "ARRET W", "ARRET X"],
    letter: "T",
    message: "Eh bien, ça en fait des colonnes !"
  },

  {
    id: 9,
    question: "QUESTION 9",
    answers: ["reponse 9"],
    stops: ["ARRET Y", "ARRET Z", "ARRET A1"],
    letter: "R",
    message: "Eh bien, ça en fait des colonnes !"
  },

  {
    id: 10,
    question: "QUESTION 10",
    answers: ["reponse 10"],
    stops: ["ARRET B1", "ARRET C1", "ARRET D1"],
    letter: "E",
    message: "Eh bien, ça en fait des colonnes !"
  },

  {
    id: 11,
    question: "QUESTION 11",
    answers: ["reponse 11"],
    stops: ["ARRET E1", "ARRET F1", "ARRET G1"],
    letter: "T",
    message: "Eh bien, ça en fait des colonnes !"
  },

  {
    id: 12,
    question: "QUESTION 12",
    answers: ["reponse 12"],
    stops: ["ARRET H1", "ARRET I1", "ARRET J1"],
    letter: "E",
    message: "Eh bien, ça en fait des colonnes !"
  },

  {
    id: 13,
    question: "QUESTION 13",
    answers: ["reponse 13"],
    stops: ["ARRET K1", "ARRET L1", "ARRET M1"],
    letter: "M",
    message: "Eh bien, ça en fait des colonnes !"
  },

  {
    id: 14,
    question: "QUESTION 14",
    answers: ["reponse 14"],
    stops: ["ARRET N1", "ARRET O1", "ARRET P1"],
    letter: "O",
    message: "Eh bien, ça en fait des colonnes !"
  },

  {
    id: 15,
    question: "QUESTION 15",
    answers: ["reponse 15"],
    stops: ["ARRET Q1", "ARRET R1", "ARRET S1"],
    letter: "I",
    message: "Eh bien, ça en fait des colonnes !"
  },

  {
    id: 16,
    question: "QUESTION 16",
    answers: ["reponse 16"],
    stops: ["ARRET T1", "ARRET U1", "ARRET V1"],
    letter: "N",
    message: "Eh bien, ça en fait des colonnes !"
  }

];
